angelmakeups.com 2016-05-15

# Privacy Policy - Angelmakeups

“Privacy can be invaded” this statement describes how the personal information collected through our websites are protected. The terms “we” and “us” refer to ANGELMAKEUPS BEAUTY & HEALTHCARE. which is part of the Terms of Use, which governs your use of the websites, and is located here.

###### ANGELMAKEUPS BEAUTY & HEALTHCARE.

Values the privacy of those who use our websites and makes all commercially reasonable efforts to protect it. This Privacy Policy covers the collection, use and disclosure of personal information that may be collected any time you interact with the Angelmakeups, websites such as when you are using our applications or purchase our products and services, or communicate with our employees and representatives.

BY INSTALLING, USING OR OTHERWISE ACCESSING ANGELMAKEUPS, YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY CEASE AND DESIST USE OF THE WEBSITE AND/OR APPLICATIONS. Provider reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at reasonable times, so please review it frequently. Your continued use of Angelmakeups will signify your acceptance of the changes to this Privacy Policy.

###### **INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT:**

**Personal Data.**

You will be asked to provide us certain information related to You (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes, without limitation: (1) “Contact Data” (such as Your name and email address,); and (2) “Demographic Data” (such as Your gender, birthday, zip code, country, height, weight, lifestyle and exercise frequency). The Personal Information you provide is used for such purposes as allowing you to set up a user account and profile, delivering software updates and special offers as well as provide convenient and personalized user access and improve the features and usability of our products. Registered users can view and change their personal information at any time by entering the.

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, and under the following circumstances, Provider will keep Your Personal Information private, and will not share it with third parties.

You are under no obligation to provide Personal Information, with the caveat that your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain of the services.

###### **Non-personal data.**

You can contribute to our websites in a number of different ways, including writing reviews, uploading videos and photos, participating in question and answers, tagging products, filling out your public profile, and voting on other users’ contributions. We may store these contributions (your “Public Content”), display them to other users, and use them for promotional purposes. Note that if you include personally identifiable information in your Public Content, it can be used and viewed by others. We are not responsible for the information you choose to include in your Public Content.

Provider may also use tools or third party analytical software to collect and use certain non-personal data that does not enable Provider to identify you. The types of non-personal data Provider may collect and use include, but are not limited to: (i) browser name, version or type; (ii) operating system details; (iii) mobile device type and device properties; (iv) mobile device software platform and firmware; (v) mobile phone carrier; (vi) geographical data no more accurate that metropolitan areas; (vii) other non-personal data as reasonably required by Provider to enhance its services.

Provider may use the collected data for purposes of analysing usage of Angelmakeups, managing and providing Angelmakeups and to further develop services and products. Application provider reserves the right to use and disclose the collected non-personal data for purposes of advertisement by Provider or Provider’s partners.

###### **Messaging.**

The websites and apps allow you to exchange messages with others using the messaging features and/or email. We may store these messages in order to deliver them and allow you to manage them.

###### **Inviting friends.**

You can invite your friends to join the websites by providing their contact information, or by entering your log-in credentials to import your address book from other sites. We may store and use your friends’ contact information to invite them to join and connect with you on our services. But we do not save your login credentials. Your friends will always have the opportunity to opt-out of receiving further emails from us.

###### **Third party services.**

We allow you to access third party services, such as Facebook, pinterest and Twitter, to share your selected Public Content with those services, and import information about who you are connected with on those other services so you can connect with them on the websites or mobile. You can always opt out on your account page. Some of those third party services may also provide us with information from your accounts there to enhance and personalize your use of our products. For example, you can allow Facebook to tell us who your Facebook friends are so you can follow their activity on our websites and apps. You can also further modify your privacy settings with those other services directly. For example, you can adjust your privacy setting on Facebook to prevent your Facebook friends from sharing information about you from their Facebook accounts with our websites.

###### **Activity and log data.**

For Websites – We automatically store information related to your use of the Site, such as the pages you view on the Site, your browser type, IP address, requested URL, browser language, referring URL, and the date and time of your visits. We use this type of information to administer the Site and provide the better service to you. We also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behaviour and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Site or to manage or improve the Site.

###### **Cookies**

For websites – We send cookies to your computer in order to uniquely identify your browser and improve the quality of our service. “Cookies” refer to small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing the Site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). Persistent cookies can be removed by following your browser help file directions. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Site may not work properly or at all. Our cookies are linked to your information, such as your name, email address and password. We enable some of our business partners to use cookies in conjunction with your use of the Site. We have no access to or control over the use of these cookies. These cookies collect information about your use of the Site, such as where you came from, which pages you visited within the Site, and possibly other sites you visit if those sites cooperate with the same third party, but do not collect your name, email address, contact information or other personally identifiable information that by itself would allow the third party to identify or contact you.

###### **Feedback**

You should feel free to give us feedback, register a complaint, or ask questions about the websites or the mobile apps. We may store your communications, including any personal information you include in them, so that we can effectively respond to you.

###### **Administration**

We may use the information described above for routine administrative purposes, such as investigating abuses on our products, responding to user inquiries and enforcing and applying our Terms of Service and Statement.

###### **Data storage**

We store data in USA.

###### **TRANSFER OF INFORMATION:**

###### **Public Content.**

Certain portions of the Website and Applications are open to any viewer, such as our community forums and your personal profile. Any information you post in these locations may be available and accessible to other members. In addition, the websites and applications contain features that permit you to upload, post, transmit, display, perform or distribute content, information or other data, including your personal information. Any information that you choose to disclose by means of such features becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information by means of such features, and you agree to assume all responsibility for doing so.

If you post content for public view on the websites or mobile apps, we may distribute such public content to a wider audience by sharing it (or portions of it) with third parties so that they can publish it on their own websites and media platforms. We may ask them to credit you as the source of these contributions by including your account name and profile photo.

###### **Third party service providers.**

We may use third parties to provide technical and customer support, perform tracking and reporting functions, conduct quality assurance testing, perform payment processing and provide other services in connection with the websites. We may share information about you with them so that they can perform the services they are required to perform, but they are not permitted to use your personal information other than to provide the services requested by you.

###### **Third party advertising.**

Third parties serve some of the ads on our websites. We do not send any individualized personal information to them, but they may have access to information that they obtain through cookies or that you share with them yourself. Note that we do not rent, share, sell or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

Google AdSense is used on Angelmakeups.com. Adsense serves ads based on the content of the sites you view. As you browse websites that have partnered with Google or Google sites, such as YouTube, Google may place a cookie in your browser to track the types of pages visited or content that you viewed. Based on this information, Google associates your browser with relevant interest categories and uses these categories to show interest-based ads. For example, if you frequently visit travel websites, Google may show more ads related to travel. Google will not associate sensitive interest categories with your browser (such as those based on race, religion, sexual orientation, health, or sensitive financial categories), and will not use such categories when showing you interest-based ads.

Opting out of interest-based advertising : If you prefer not to receive interest-based advertising, you can click on the “Opt out” button on the Google Ads Preferences Manager Page. Google also offers a number of options to permanently save your opt-out settings in your browser. After you opt out, Google will not collect interest category information and you will not receive interest-based ads.

DoubleClick DART Cookie Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Angelmakeups.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Angelmakeups.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL –http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

• Google Adsense  
• Commission Junction  
• Widget Bucks  
• Adbrite  
• Clickbank  
• Azoogle  
• Chitika  
• Linkshare  
• Amazon  
• Kontera

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Angelmakeups.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. Angelmakeups.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Angelmakeups.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

###### **Aggregate information**

We may share non-personal information in the aggregate to third parties relating to user behaviour in connection with actual or prospective business relationship with those third parties, such as advertisers and content distributors. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, advertising banners.

###### **Business transfers**

We may share your information with our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control that we may have now or in the future, in which case we will require them to honour this Statement. If another company acquires our company or all or substantially all of our assets, that company will possess your information, and will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Statement.

###### **Investigations**

We reserve the right to investigate abuses on websites or mobile apps, and enforce and apply our Terms of Service and Statement. We may disclose information about you to third parties if we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) take action regarding suspected illegal activities; (b) enforce or apply our Terms of Service and Statement; (c) comply with legal process and law enforcement instructions and orders, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on us; or (d) protect our rights, reputation, and property, or that of our users, affiliates, or the public.

###### **Data Security**

Provider is committed to protecting the security of Your information and takes reasonable precautions to protect it. However, Internet data transmissions, whether wired or wireless, cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure and as a result we cannot ensure the security of information You transmit to us; accordingly, You acknowledge that You do so at Your own risk. Once we receive Your data transmission, we make all commercially reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems.

###### **Links to Third Party Sites or Application**

Provider may make available links through advertisements or otherwise enabling you to access third party sites or applications. Please note that, while using such sites or applications, you are using sites or applications developed and administered by people or companies not affiliated with or controlled by us. Provider is not responsible for the actions of those people or companies, the content of their sites or applications, the use of information you provide to them, or any products or services they may offer. Our link to those sites does not constitute our sponsorship of, or affiliation with, those people or companies.

We suggest you read the privacy policies on all such third party websites.

###### **Children’s privacy**

The websites and the mobile apps are intended for general audiences and is not directed to children under 13. Provider does not solicit or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If Provider becomes aware that it has collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13 without parental consent, Provider will take steps to remove such information and terminate the child’s account. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at [**contact@angelmakeups.com**](mailto:contact@angelmakeups.com).

###### **Consent to receive email from DietPoint**

By registering with the Website and/or Applications, You thereby consent to receive periodic email communications from Provider regarding the Services, new product offers, promotions and other matters. As part of registration, you may also elect to receive periodic newsletters. You may opt-out of receiving newsletters at any time by (a) following the unsubscribe instructions contained in each newsletter; or (b) changing the email preferences in your account.

However, despite any requests to close your account or your indicated email preferences, we may still need to contact you as required by law or on legal matters, for example to inform you of any updates to our Terms of Service or this Statement.

###### **DISPUTE RESOLUTION:**

If you believe that Angel Makeups has not adhered to this Statement you may write to the Angel Makeups Privacy following address:

Contact us via email at [**contact@angelmakeups.com**](mailto:contact@angelmakeups.com)

###### **MODIFICATIONS TO THIS STATEMENT:**

We may revise this Statement from time to time. The most current version of the Statement will govern our use of your information and will always be located here. If we make a change to this Statement that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes prior to implementing the change on the Site and/or via the email associated with your account. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Statement.
